Have you ever taken a sickie?
你曾经请过（一天的）病假吗？
If so, what did you say to your boss?
如果是的话，你对老板说了什么？
It seems many people in the UK like to blame their pets for their absence.
似乎许多英国人喜欢把缺勤的责任推给他们的宠物。
One person said they couldn't come to work because their rabbit was missing.
有个人说他们不能来上班，因为他们的兔子不见了。
Perhaps that was a white lie; this next one though sounds more like a porky.
也许那是个无恶意的谎话；不过接下来这个听起来更像是个谎话。
A worker said that he couldn't come to work because he had to take his dog to the vet.
一名员工说他不能来上班，因为他得带他的狗去看兽医（veterinary的简写）。
This might seem reasonable - apart from the fact that the man told his boss his dog was dead as a previous excuse for skiving off.
这听起来可能很合理——除了他曾经以他的狗死了为借口偷懒这件事之外。
If you've ever worked as a teacher, you'll know that children can be very creative when it comes to excuses for not doing their homework.
如果你曾经当过老师，你会知道孩子们在找借口不写作业时非常有创意。
Once again, it's popular to blame pets.
再一次，把责任推给宠物是很受欢迎的做法。
According to a BBC survey, almost 10 percent of excuses involve pets eating the assignment.
根据BBC的一项调查，几乎10%的借口涉及宠物吃掉了作业。
"The dog ate my homework" is a legendary excuse - no one is sure if a student has ever really used it.
“狗吃了我的作业”是一个非常著名的借口——没人确定是否有学生真的用过这个借口。
But it's not just workplaces and schools which attract fibbers.
但不仅仅是工作场所和学校会吸引说小谎者。
People caught claiming welfare benefits illegally have also tried to con the authorities.
那些被抓住非法申领福利金的人也试图欺骗当局。
A husband whose wife was working while also on the dole said that he didn't know she had a job because he was always in the garden shed during working hours.
一个妻子在工作的同时也在领取救济金，她丈夫说，他不知道她有工作，因为在工作时间，他总是在花园棚屋里。
There are many more ridiculous excuses people have made for not doing the things they were supposed to do.
人们为了不做他们应该做的事情编造了更多荒谬的借口。
But there isn't enough room on this page to fit them all.
但这页纸的空间不足以容纳所有借口。
And besides, I can't carry on because… the cat's eaten my keyboard.
而且，我也不能继续写下去了，因为……猫吃了我的键盘。
What about you: what's your excuse?
你呢：你的借口是什么？